almost hijacked the last one with a new
idea so I wanted to record it here with
the everything library I'm talking about
how there's two libraries in different
cities and I'm often inspired by the
ideas that have an accessory in like
Portland in Seattle I'm going to write
here about an idea
and we like to see it here I just think
it's less efficient for everyone to have
to start from zero so if all of the two
libraries around the world could
coordinate find out what works and what
doesn't work and use databases that one
of them created so that they can all use
it and so coordination between
nonprofits for solutions that work one
of the other solutions we have here
which is amazing and I've definitely
utilized is quest which is a non-profit
grocery store so a lot of the food that
would go to waste because it's close to
the expiry date or about to go off in
case of produce and dairy and eggs and
such is donated and then it's sold at a
very low cost to people who have a
referral to shop there so it is a step
up or step sideways or whatever from the
food bank or you're given food for free
but you have no autonomy on what you're
really given and quest you can go to and
shop for your own food a lot of it here
because of our local grocery shops is a
is organic produce that's you have to
use in the next couple days but to be
able to help other cities start
something like that easily would be
amazing if quest could could put that
out there
the programs do we have no other
programs I can't think of any here at
this exact moment time that come into
mind but when one city comes up with a
solution being able to roll that out in
other cities more easily by building on
what has already been done and not
reinventing the wheel
so non-profit and solution corporation
knowledge share that is Apple 39